<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="plugins_title">OctoPrint\'s plugins</string>

    <string name="plugins_help_title">OctoPrint\'s plugins</string>
    <string name="plugins_help_message">This is the list of plugins currently integrated in Printoid.\n\nAll OctoPrint\'s plugin are not implemented in Printoid and I (the developer) can not integrated them all.\n\nPlease contact me at printoid.for.octoprint@gmail.com if you would like to see a new plugin in Printoid. I will reflect on its integration (if and only it is possible).</string>

    <string name="plugin_desc_psu">This OctoPrint plugin controls an ATX/AUX power supply to help reduce power consumption and noise when the printer is not in use.</string>
    <string name="plugin_desc_autoshutdown">Plugin for automatically shutting down the system after print is finished. Can be configured only when the server is up.</string>
    <string name="plugin_desc_tp_link">Work inspired by OctoPrint-PSUControl and TP-Link WiFi SmartPlug Client, this plugin controls a TP-Link Smartplug via OctoPrint\'s nav bar.</string>
    <string name="plugin_desc_enclosure">Control pretty much everything that you might want to do on your Raspberry Pi/OctoPrint/Enclosure.</string>
    <string name="plugin_desc_navbartemp">Display temperatures on OctoPrint\'s navigation bar. For Raspberry Pi users, this plugin allows to show the Raspberry Pi\'s CPU temperature in the app title bar automatically.</string>

    <string name="plugin_message_psu">The PSU Control plugin shall be installed on your OctoPrint server. Then it will automatically appear in the left menu of the app.</string>
    <string name="plugin_message_tp_link">The TP-Link SmartPlug shall should be installed on your OctoPrint server. Then it will automatically appear in the left menu of the app.\nAdjust its behavior from the settings of Printoid.</string>
    <string name="plugin_message_enclosure">This plugin will be integrated very soon in Printoid!</string>
    <string name="plugin_message_navbartemp">The Navbar Temp plugin should be installed on your OctoPrint server.\n\nThen if you are using a Raspberry Pi, its CPU temperature will appear automatically in the app\'s title bar.</string>
    <string name="plugin_desc_octolapse">Octolapse is designed to make stabilized timelapses of your prints with as little hassle as possible, and it\'s extremely configurable. Now you can create a silky smooth timelapse without a custom camera mount, no GCode customizations required.</string>

    <string name="plugin_not_available">This plugin seems not available (or not installed on your OctoPrint server). Please check its status on your OctoPrint server\'s settings.</string>

    <!-- AUTOMATIC SHUTDOWN PLUGIN -->
    <string name="plugin_autoshutdown_enable">Shutdown server after print finishes</string>
    <string name="plugin_autoshutdown_type">Type</string>

    <!-- PSU CONTROL PLUGIN -->
    <string name="plugin_psu_enable">Enable PSU</string>

    <!-- TPLINK SMARTPLUG PLUGIN -->
    <string name="plugin_tplink_enable">Enable TP-Link SmartPlug</string>

    <!-- NAVBARTEMP PLUGIN -->
    <string name="plugin_navbartemp_temperature">System SoC temperature</string>

    <!-- OCTOLAPSE PLUGIN -->
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_enable">Enable Octolapse</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_status">Status:</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_printer">Printer:</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_stabilization">Stabilization:</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_snapshot">Snapshot:</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_rendering">Rendering:</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_camera">Camera:</string>
    <string name="plugin_octolapse_debug">Debug:</string>

</resources>